talash.com 2015-09-30

# Privacy Policy

We, at Talash.com (TIPL), and all our subsidiaries respect your privacy and make all attempts to secure your information. This privacy policy provides a brief introduction about what information is collected and how it is used. You will be advised to thoroughly read the privacy policy. By using Talash.com (TIPL) you certify that you agree with the suggested collection and use of your information (as provided in the Privacy Policy). 

INFORMATION THAT IS OR MAY BE COLLECTED

You can easily browse through our website without providing your personal information. If that is the case, certain information about your visit might be stored with us. Such collected information can include but not limited to:

  * IP Address 
  * Browser and / or operating system used
  * Date and time of site access 
  * Pages visited 
  * If you visited our website through a link on another website then that website’s URL

This information will not manage to identify you personally nor would it be anytime linked back to you. 

You might be required to submit more information if you are registering with our website. In that case, the information collected might include but not limited to:

  * First and Last name 
  * Email address (primary and alternate) 
  * Mobile Number and other contact number 
  * Address 
  * Demographic Profile 
  * Preferences & Interests 
  * Financial Information 
  * Opinion on features of our website 

You might, at any time, decide to delete or deactivate the account. Your information, however, will stay stored in the archives on our server even after such deletion, termination or deactivation. 

MEANS OF INFORMATION COLLECTION 

While most of your information might be collected and stored by us, our advertisers might also capture anonymous information about site traffic and other related information. 

INFORMATION USE 

You can be completely relieved about the information about you that is captured by Talash.com (TIPL). We will not share, rent, sell or trade your personally identifiable data with any third party without your written consent unless it is set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

Your information, anonymous and personally identifiable, shall be used for some of the following but not limited purposes:

  * To personalize your buying experience 
  * To update you when there are offers we think you might be interested in 
  *   * To get in touch with you for various reasons 
  *   * To abide to any legal requirements 
  *   * To conduct research 
  *   * To better our services in order to better satisfy you 
  *   * To notify you if you win any contest 
  *   * Send you promotional material from our contest sponsors and / or advertisers 
  *   * Track your session to find out the most popular section 
  *   * To develop new offerings 
  *   * To help process your requests
  * 

There could be various other utilities of your collected information. For the fulfilment of the above mentioned purposes, we might be required, from time to time, to share your information with our corporate affiliates, dealers, agents, vendors and other third parties. We might also share your information with the advertisers but on an aggregate basis only. 

OPTIONAL

Not all of the use of information is mandatory. You might wish to block certain usages of your information. 

Firstly, supplying personal information is completely voluntary and you can even access our website without providing the same. However, certain functionalities of the site are only restricted to registered users. (To be a registered user you need to submit some minimum required personal information). 

You might decide to block your personally identifiable information from our database. In this case, your registration will be cancelled. However, the information might stay in the archives on our server.

You also have complete control over receiving advertising messages from Talash.com or our advertisers and associates. You can simply opt out of any such programme to do so. 

COOKIES

From time to time, we might place ‘cookies’ on your personal computer. Cookies are nothing but identifiers which are generally saved on your computer’s hard drive. They help us identify you when you visit our website again. On the basis of the same, we can provide suggestions and even customize the offering. Cookies might even be used to track your visit and analyze your satisfaction with site usage. You can, however, decide to reject cookies. This you can do by altering the settings of your browser, which generally are automatically set on ‘Accept Cookies’ mode. By rejecting cookies, some of the functionalities of the website might not work properly or not at all. 

THIRD PARTY LINKS 

There are links on our website which direct you towards third party websites. Given that these websites are not controlled by Talash.com, they might be expected to have their separate privacy policy and ways of managing information. Therefore, once you have left the server of Talash.com (which you can detect by identifying the URL on the location tab of your browser), we hold no responsibility of the collection, capturing and sharing of your information. You will be advised to check that particular site’s privacy policy before offering information. In case, you can’t find the privacy policy through the home page of the website; you can directly contact the website authorities to know the way forward. 

INFORMATION SECURITY MEASURES 

The security of your information is imperative and we have physical, electronic and managerial procedures in place to do the same. Sensitive information is encrypted to maintain its security. Moreover, only authorized personnel are allowed an access to the server where your information is stored. Information might also be shared with other personnel and sometimes third parties on a need to know basis to complete a transaction or attend to your service request or any other reasons. 

Despite such efforts, you are required to understand that transmission done through the internet is never 100% secure. Therefore, we have no liability or accountability for the disclosure or loss of your information because of transmission errors or unauthorized / illicit acts by third parties. 

INFORMATION ALTERATION 

If there is an inaccuracy in your information that you wish to change or make some necessary amendments, you can do it online. In case of any problems in doing so, you can even contact us through email or telephone. 

OPT OUT 

You can mail us at [privacy@talash.com](mailto:privacy@talash.com) if you do not wish to receive any further information from us. 

PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES 

Changes to this privacy policy can be made at the sole discretion of Talash.com and without any intimation of the same. You are suggested to continuously visit this page to keep yourself updated with the changes. 

QUERIES & FEEDBACK 

In case you have any queries, you can contact us at [support@talash.com](mailto:support@talash.com).

If you have any feedback for us, do provide the same at [feedback@talash.com](mailto:feedback@talash.com).
